<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>blanksy .org</title>
    <link>https://blanksy.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on blanksy .org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 17:13:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blanksy.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Graffiti</title>
      <link>https://blanksy.org/posts/graffiti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 12:21:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blanksy.org/posts/graffiti/</guid>
      <description>Graffiti (singular graffiti or graffito, the latter only used in graffiti archeology) is writing or drawings made on a wall or other surface, usually without permission [see bullying] and within public view.
Modern graffiti is a controversial subject.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leave no trace</title>
      <link>https://blanksy.org/posts/leave-no-trace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 17:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blanksy.org/posts/leave-no-trace/</guid>
      <description>When you&amp;rsquo;re out hiking in the woods (or anywhere, actually) the concept of Leave no trace means exactly what it sounds like. Leave no trace. Leave no garbage, litter, detritus, or crap of your own behind to spoil the environment and mar the experience of the next person who comes along.
Better still &amp;ndash; if someone else leaves their crap behind, pack that out too, if you can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leave the gate as you found it</title>
      <link>https://blanksy.org/posts/leave-the-gate-as-you-found-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 12:13:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blanksy.org/posts/leave-the-gate-as-you-found-it/</guid>
      <description>Leave the gate as you found it (or leave all gates as found) is an important rule of courtesy in rural areas throughout the world. If a gate is found open, it should be left open, and if it is closed, it should be left closed. If a closed gate absolutely must be traversed, it should be closed again afterwards. It applies to visitors travelling onto or across farms, ranches, and stations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bullying</title>
      <link>https://blanksy.org/posts/bully/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 17:13:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blanksy.org/posts/bully/</guid>
      <description>To cause (someone) to do something by means of force or coercion.
In the case of graffiti, one forces others to, &amp;ldquo;Look at me! Look at me!&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://blanksy.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 15:05:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blanksy.org/about/</guid>
      <description>I don&amp;rsquo;t like bullying behaviour, even when it&amp;rsquo;s ostensibly for a &amp;lsquo;good cause&amp;rsquo;.
The problem (as always) with &amp;lsquo;a good cause&amp;rsquo; is that your good cause may not be the same as my good cause.
One person&amp;rsquo;s artistic political expression is another person&amp;rsquo;s propaganda.
Same goes for art. Maybe I don&amp;rsquo;t want a cute girl with a heart balloon adorning my concrete canvas.
Paint on your wall if you want. Looks great!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
